Finding Aid for University Planner's Office (University of Michigan) records, 1940-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Projects, 1950-2008
  - Traffic, Transportation and Parking
    - Streets and Intersections
      - East Washington Street Traffic Study (re: impact of Central Campus expansion on Ann Arbor traffic and parking), 1963-1964 (Box 8)
        (includes 6 b&w photos)
      - Fifth Avenue and Division Street, 1967 (Box 8)
      - Forest/Observatory/Huron Intersection, 1961-1971 (Box 8)
      - Fuller Parkway, 1965-1982 (Box 8)
      - Glen/Huron/Fletcher Intersection, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
      - Hill Street, 1968-1972 (Box 8)
      - North University Street, 1963 (Box 8)
      - State Street, 1964-1967 (Box 8)
      - Thompson/Monroe/Packard Intersection, 1967-1973 (Box 8)
      - Washtenaw/Geddes/Church Intersection, 1960-1962, 1977 (Box 8)
      - Washtenaw/Huron Intersection, 1974 (Box 8)
    - Student Vehicle Regulations, 1959, 1967-1968
      - Joint UM-City Committee on Student Vehicle Registration, 1968 (Box 43)
    - Toilet Facilities Survey, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Traffic Counting Program, 1963-1969 (Box 8)
    - Reports
      - "Proposal to University of Michigan for a Central Campus Parking Study" (Bennett-Ringrose-Wolsfield-Jarvis-Gardner, Inc.), 1988 (Box 8)
      - "A Traffic and Parking Analysis, The Ann Arbor Thoroughfare Plan in Relation to University of Michigan Central Campus Study" (Harland Bartholomew and Associates), 1964 (Box 8)
    - Mass Transit Conference, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Street Projects
      - Fuller Parkway Alignment Study, 1965 (Box 41)
      - Observatory Extension, 1984 (Box 41)
      - State Street Mall, 1980 (Box 41)
    - Geddes/Fuller/Conrail Corridor Study (Box 44)
      - Final Report, 1994 (Box 44)
      - Appendices, 1994 (Box 44)
      - Forest Avenue Improvements (Box 45)
        - General, 1965-1976 (Box 45)
        - Feasibility Study, 1965 (Box 45)
      - Huron Parkway Corridor, 1963-1969 (Box 45)
      - Southern Penetrator Route Study, 1966-1972 (Box 45)
    - Veterans Administration Hospital, 1987-1993
      - Fuller Road/Oak Way Proposals, 1991 (Box 45)
      - Fuller/Oak Way Relocation Report, 1992 (Box 45)
      - Fuller/Oak Way Traffic Analysis, 1992 (Box 45)
    - Service Center Sites
      - South Service Site, 1974 (Box 41)
      - Hospital Administrative Center, 1969 (Box 41)
      - North Campus Site, 1966-1974 (Box 41)
      - Satellite Service Centers, 1969 (Box 41)
    - Schoenberg Archives, 1971 (Box 41)
    - Information Center on the Diag, 1964-1969 (Box 41)
    - Gateway Study, 1991-1992 (Box 41)
    - Washtenaw Terrace, 1963 (Box 41)
    - Residential Rehabilitation, 1989 (Box 41)
    - Science Building, 1967-1968 (Box 41)
    - Buildings in Mental Retardation, 1979 (Box 41)
    - Center for Human Growth and Development, 1967 (Box 41)
    - Crew Club, 1980-1982 (Box 41)
    - Food Service Consolidation, 1978 (Box 41)
    - Biological Sciences, 1959 (Box 41)
    - Stadium Area Study, 1972 (Box 41)
    - Commercial Service Center, 1967-1973 (Box 41)
    - North Campus
      - Concert Hall, undated (Box 41)
      - Outdoor Recreation Areas, 1969-1973 (Box 41)
    - Pedestrian Studies, 1988 (Box 41)
    - Museums Expansions, 1985 (Box 41)
    - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, 1980-1981, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Development Potential Southwest Central Campus, 1971 (Box 41)
    - Recreational Open Space, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Michigan High School Coaches Hall of Fame, 1995 (Box 41)
    - High School Site Study, 1962 (Box 41)
    - Hubbard Field Proposed Land Trade, 1991 (Box 41)
    - Site Proposal for High Energy Accelerator, 1956 (Box 41)
    - Health Maintenance Organization Building, 1981 (Box 43)
    - Michigan Sanitary Engineering Laboratory, ca. 1960 (Box 43)
    - Planning Buildings
      - Undergraduate Astronomy Center, 1971 (Box 43)
      - University Library Supplements to Report, 1960 (Box 43)
      - International Studies Building, 1974 (Box 43)
      - Cancer Research Center, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
      - Center for Public Policy Studies, 1974 (Box 43)
      - U of M Residential College, 1963-1966 (Box 44)
      - College of Engineering
        - 1959-1983, 5 folders (Box 44)
        - Program Analysis, 1971 (Box 44)
        - Site and Building Plans for an Engineering and Technology Center, 1967 (Box 44)
        - Plans for Developing an Engineering and Technology Center on The North Campus, 1966 (Box 44)
        - A Program to Strengthen Engineering Education at the University of Michigan, 1974 (Box 44)
        - Program Statement Building I Preliminary Report, 1969 (Box 44)
        - Program Statement Building I Final Report, 1969 (Box 44)
        - Pre-Prospectus Buildings III and IV, 1976 (Box 44)
        - Prospectus Building I, 1975 (Box 44)
    - Campus Walkway Projects East University, 1967-2004 (Box 43)
    - Diag Renovation, 1992-1997 (Box 43)
    - Ingalls Mall
      - Street Projects, 1964-1989 (Box 43)
      - Landscape Projects, 1965-1991 (Box 43)
    - Recreation Areas
      - 1965-1976 (Box 43)
      - North Campus, 1966-1991 (Box 43)
    - Regents' Plaza, 1963-1969 (Box 43)
    - Campus Lighting, 1992-1997 (Box 43)
    - Landscape Project Monroe Mall, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
    - Associated Agencies Land Assignments, 1963-1968 (Box 43)
    - Pedestrian Connector, 1966-1992 (Box 43)
    - Aquarium, 1992-1998 (Box 44)
    - South State Street Property, 1992 (Box 45)